Guide to the Joseph R. Starobin and Robert S. Starobin Papers, 1945-1976
Department of Special Collections
- Series I: Joseph Starobin
  - Subseries 4: Joseph Starobin's whole newspapers. Stored in flat print boxes.
    - 57 items total, plus 2 separate folders, as described. (Oversize 10)
    - Folder containing US newspapers and clippings originally collected together for their articles about US strike. Nov. 1945-Jan 1946. (Oversize 10, Folder 1)
    - Folder containing US newspapers marking important dates in World War II. (Oversize 10, Folder 2)
    - The subseries also contains editions of the following newspapers: Daily Worker (Primarily CPA Discussion pages) (Oversize 10, Folder 3)
      - Denver Post
      - Greeley Daily Tribune and Greeley Republican
      - Guild Daily (Seattle, American Newspaper Guild)
      - Militant
      - Missoula Sentinel
      - Morning Oregonian
      - New York Times
      - New York World Telegram
      - News-Telegram (Portland, OR)
      - Petal Paper
      - Public Service Sentinel (Seattle)
      - San Francisco Chronicle
      - San Francisco News
      - Times, Science Review
      - Washington State Labor News
    - Pages 3, 4 of the Daily Worker. Most dates March 1956-January 1957. Page 4 is "Speak Your Piece," the letters to the editor page. (Oversize 10.5)
- Series II: Robert Starobin
  - Subseries I: Personal life
    - Biographical materials (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - -Personality in Politics: the Commitment of a Suicide - Linda Rennie Forcey. (Dissertation, SUNY-Binghampton, 1978) (bought and added to collection by aGatherin') 1978
      - -Roots of Radicalism: Jews, Christians, and the New Left - S. Rothman and S. R. Lichter., Photocopy of pages 139-143 about RS.
      - -Photocopy of biographical sketch which appeared preceding RS's article "Racism and the American Experience" in Radical America, Vol. 5, no. 2, March-April 1971. He committed suicide right before this piece appeared. 1971 Mar.-Apr.
      - -Dealer's biographical sketch.
    - Note from Norma to Bob, and article 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 2 Commencement programs, Bronx High School of Science, 1957. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Dynamo, Bronx High School of Science literary magazine. 1957 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: Chemistry (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: Chemistry (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: Social Studies (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: Social Studies (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: Biology (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: History, Physics (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Bronx High School of Science notes: English, Social Studies (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Cornell notes: Math (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Cornell notes (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Cornell notes (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Science manuals, publications (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Science manuals, publications (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Subseries II: Academic life and Research
    - University of Wisconsin-Madison Materials
      - UW-M faculty meetings (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - UW-M faculty and student memos, protest issues (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - UW-M History Dept. notes (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - UW-M History Dept. faculty meeting minutes (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - UW-M History Dept. faculty meeting minutes and memos (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - UW-M History Dept. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - UW-M grading controversy (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - UW-M grading controversy (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - UW-M grading controversy (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - UW-M History Dept. - Cronon (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - UW-M reports on student unrest (Mermin Report); course and teacher evaluations 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - UW-M reports on graduates (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - UW-M Teaching Assistants Association (TAA) (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - UW-M History Students Association (HSA) (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - UW Wisconsin Professors for Peace (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - UW-M Daily Cardinal letter (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - UW-M Radical fliers (Box 13, Folder 17)
        - see also Box 27 for more radical materials.
      - UW-M Oshkosh students controversy (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - "Student proposal for political organizing" 1968 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Prospectus for a socialist review (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - University of Wisconsin-Madison Teaching
      - UW-M campus report with bibliography of "Black America" (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Notes for RS's course UW-M History 631 - History of the Blues. 1969 Spr. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Student paper for History 611 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Student papers (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Student papers (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Student papers (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Articles of Confederation, 1777., Photocopy. (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Photocopies of typed slave letters to be used in teaching. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Bobbs-Merrill Reprint Series in History:, 10 items (Box 14, Folder 9)
        - articles on various topics in American history.
      - "Confessions of Nat Turner, 1831." (Box 14, Folder 10)
        - Reserve text for RS course.
      - "Vesey Trial" - Reserve text for RS course., 2 copies. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - "The Legacy of Slavery and the Roots of Black Nationalism," by Eugene D. Genovese. - Reserve text for RS course. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Robert Starobin Publications
      - RS's "Racism and the American Experience." In Radical America, issue on black labor. Vol. 5, no.2. Mar./Apr. 1971, p. 93-110. 1971 Mar.-Apr., 3 copies. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - RS's "Economics of Industrial Slavery in the 1970 Summer Old South." Reprint from Business History Review Vol. XLIV, no. 2, Summer 1970. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - RS's "Disciplining Slaves in the Old South." In Journal of Negro History, Vol. LIII, no. 2, Apr. 1968., 2 reprints. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - RS's "The Negro: a central theme in American history." In Journal of Contemporary History Vol. 3, no. 2, 1968. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - RS's "Privileged Bondsmen and the Process of Accommodation: the role of houseservants and drivers as seen in their own letters." In Journal of Social History, Fall 1981. (Box 15, Folder 5)
        Journal and reprint.
      - RS's "Race Relations in Old South Industries." In American Negro Slavery - a modern reader. Weinstein and Gatell, eds. NY: Oxford UP, 1968., 2 photocopies. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Reviews of RS's Industrial Slavery in the Old South. (Box 15, Folder 7)
        1- journal unknown; 2- Journal of Interdisciplinary History, 20 Nov. 1972. Review by Robert Brandfon.
    - Research materials for Industrial Slavery in the Old South.
      In original order of binder from which they were removed.
      - Research materials for Industrial Slavery in the Old South book. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Research materials for book. (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Research materials for book. Photocopies of slave letters. (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Research materials for book. Photocopies of slave letters. (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Research materials for book. Photocopies of slave letters. (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Research materials for Industrial Slavery in the Old South and articles (except Vesey article). (Box 17)
      - Research materials. Material on Garnet. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Research materials. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Research materials. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Research materials. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Research materials. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Research materials. (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Research materials. Charles Colcock James Papers, Tulane University Library - not used. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Research materials. (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Research materials. Material on white fears of insurrection. (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Research materials. Note cards. (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Research materials. Note cards. (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Research materials. "Material on militant abolitionists." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 1)
      - Research materials. "from the John H. Cocke Papers, Univ. of Va." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 2)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 3)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 4)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 5)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 6)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 7)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 8)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 9)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 10)
      - Research materials. "John H. Cocke Papers." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 11)
      - B. Wall thesis: "Ebenezer Pettigrew." (Box 18 (OS), Folder 12)
      - outline of book for speech. n.d. (Box 18 (OS), Folder 13)
      - Appendix for book. (Box 18 (OS), Folder 14)
      - "Appendices for Chapters One and Five" (Box 18 (OS), Folder 15)
      - Oxford University Press file for book. (Box 18 (OS), Folder 16)
      - File of notecards (Box 19 (small))
      - Negatives: illustrations from Harper's for RS's book. (Box 20 (small))
      - Galleys of Vesey article. (Box 21 (OS), Folder 1)
      - Message No. 2 of Gov. Thos. Bennett (S. Carolina) to Senate and House of Rep. 28 Nov. 1822. (Box 21 (OS), Folder 2)
      - Photocopy of Southampton, Utah, minutes book. (Box 21 (OS), Folder 3)
    - Research materials for Vesey article.
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes mat'ls from McDonogh Papers, Tulane. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes mat'ls from Colcock Jones Papers. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes Reflections, Occasioned by the late Disturbances in Charleston, by Achates; and assorted letters. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes materials from Cheves Papers, South Carolina Historical Society. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes mat'ls from Ernest Haywood Papers, UNC. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Research mat'ls for Vesey article. Includes mat'ls from Arnold-Screven Papers, UNC; Hammet Papers, Duke Univ. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Research materials for Vesey article (Box 22, Folder 7)
        .
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Photocopy of An Official Report of the Trials of Sundry Negroes, charged with an attempt to raise an insurrection in the State of South Carolina. By Lionel H. Kennedy and T. Parker. (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Notecards. (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes photocopies from Drew, "The Refugee; or a North-side view of slavery." (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes a photocopy of "A letter of John McDonogh, on African colonization," 1842, Tulane University. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Letters. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 8)
        Includes a photocopy of "The Late Contemplated Insurrection in Charlestown, South Carolina... the Death of William Irving..." 1850, NYPL.
      - Research materials for Vesey article. "An Account of the Late Intended Insurrection among a portion of Blacks in the City,..." 1822. (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. "A Refutation of the Calumnies Circulated against the Southern and Western States respecting the Institution and Existence of Slavery among them," by a South Carolinian, 1822. (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. Includes letter from Bill, Univ. of Michigan, re: Vesey research; also some personal items, as per original order, artwork by RS's daughter, Rachel. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Research materials for Vesey article. (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Vesey article. Correspondence with editors. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - 2 Vesey article drafts: "Denmark Vesey's Slave Conspiracy of 1822, A Study in Rebellion and Repression," by Robert S. Starobin, Associate Professor of History, SUNY-Binghampton, 1970. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Folders 5-9 contain a typed early draft of article entitled "Denmark Vesey's Slave Conspiracy: a Documentary on the South Carolina Insurrection of 1822." "Dedicated to Bobby Seale and the Memory of Fred Hampton." Index. (Box 25, Folder 5-9)
  - Subseries III: Clippings, periodicals, pamphlets
    - African-American issues
      - Articles by Robert Blauner, UC-Berkeley."Sociology in the Courtroom: the Search for White Racism in the Huey Newman Voir Dire." (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Articles by Robert Blauner, UC-Berkeley. (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - "Colonized and Immigrant Minorities, the Third World Movement,"
        - "Towards the Decolonization of Social Research," with David Wellman.
      - Articles. African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - "Education in the Ghetto," Saturday Review. 1969 Jan.
        - "Business, Labor, and Jobs in the Ghetto," Issues in Industrial Society, vol. I, no. 1, 1969.
        - Marxism and Negro Liberalism / by Gus Hall. NY: New Century Publishers, 1951.
        - Negro Universities Press materials.
        - Dust jacket for The Black 70's by F. Barbour.
      - Articles. African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Theodore Draper. "The Fantasy of Black Nationalism," Commentary, 1969.
          Photocopy of article and resulting letters to the editor.
      - Articles. African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 5)
        New Republic articles: African-American themes.
      - Speech. African-American issues., C. Funnye. "The Untogether People: Separate but Gilded," Black Power Conference paper. "The Metropolitan Area as a Racial Problem." (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Clippings: Detroit Riots, 1967. (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Clippings: African-American Studies. (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Clippings: African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Clippings: African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Clippings: African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Clippings: African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Clippings: African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Clippings: African-American issues. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Student Protest
      - Works by RS: Student Protest. (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - "The Renaissance of Student Political Activity... The Nature of Student Activity," by RS. 1961
        - Typed notes for a lecture entitled "Treachery of Recollection; the Inner and the Outer History," dated Fall 1965. Perhaps taken by RS at Cornell. 1965
      - Works by RS: Student Protest. (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - "What has to be done?" - RS, Post-Doctoral Fellow, Cornell Society for the Humanities. ca. 1970.
        - Transcription of speech "A Year One Special - The Racial Crisis at Cornell."
        - Transcription of speech given at Cornell, n.d.
      - Photocopy of newspaper clipping: RS at rally to protest ROTC presence at Cornell. 13 May 1970. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Magnetic tape: Bookstore rally at Cornell at which RS spoke. 1970 Apr. 8 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Notes and ephemera: UC Berkeley. (Box 27, Folder 4)
        Includes Dis Orientation publication; The Regents pamphlet.
      - Clippings: Student protest. Berkeley and San Francisco State Univ. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Clippings: Student protest. UW-Madison. (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Clippings: Student protest. UW-Madison. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Clippings: Radical fliers and publications. (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Clippings: Radical fliers and publications. (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Clippings: Radical fliers and publications. (Box 27, Folder 11)
        Includes Strike Newsletter, Vol. I, no. 7,8. (Cornell ROTC protest).
      - Contents of Envelope marked SDS: (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - SDS:
        - unopened envelope addressed to RS from SDS San Francisco regional office. 1966
      - "Civil Liberties" article (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - SDS: "Report and Resolutions of the Workshop on Culture and Education: Adopted by Founding Convention of the W.E.B DuBois Clubs of America, June 21, 1964." (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - SDS: "The War on Poverty and Socialist Action Orientation" & "Political Perspectives" (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - SDS: (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - SDS Bulletin: June 1964, Oct. 1964 1964
        - PREP (Peace Research and Education Project) Fall 1964
        - Congressional Record: vol. 110:151 1964 Aug. 5
      - SDS Pamphlets (Box 27, Folder 16)
        - SDS Literature List
        - "Students and Social Action" - Tom Hayden
        - "American and the New Era" - June 1963 SDS Convention
        - "The Port Huron Settlement" - SDS
      - "Memo from the National Office" & amp; "Why the Mouse hasn't Roared" (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - New Left Politics
      - Article by RS: "Berkeley's Vigil against Nuclear Testing," Written for Liberal Democrat, 1961 Nov. 17 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        includes rejection letter.
      - Letter and Proposal to form new socialist party in the U.S. 1968 Dec. 20 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - National Conference for New Politics material. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Ad Hoc Committee for Thinking (ACT) material. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Barradas Memorandum #96 - "The Great Liberal and Conservative Misbelief." 1967 Oct. 23 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - New University Conference (NUC) materials and letter to RS from Mike James. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - NUC materials. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Material about a conference of left historians. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Letter to RS from Pablo. (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Clippings: Vietnam. (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Clippings: Vietnam. (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Clippings: Vietnam. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - General Clippings and Ephemera
      - Blues music. (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Blues music. (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Article. Theodore Marmor. "The Politics of Paying Physicians..." (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Excerpts from The Mind and Stress. (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Article reprints. (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - N. Risjord. "The Bill of Rights: Comments on its Historical Development."
      - M. Grodzins. "The Metropolitan Area as a Racial Problem."
      - Article Reprints., "This Life We Take, the Case Against Capital Punishment." (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Walter Mills. "The Permanent Peace."
      - Walter Mills. "A World Without War."
      - Article. S. M. Lipset. "The Socialism of Fools." NYT Magazine. 1971 Jan. 3 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Clippings: World events and politics. (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Clippings: World events and politics. (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Clippings: Contemporary culture. (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Book reviews. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Subseries IV: Robert Starobin's Radical Newspapers
    Whole newspapers (several copies of some) which cover the explosive events on Cornell Campus and in Ithaca over demands by black students, the Kent State killings, and student strikes in April and May 1970. Stored alphabetically in 2 flat print boxes.
    - Berkeley Barb (Box 29, Folder 1)
      IV:6 (30 June-6 Jul. 67); XI:6 (14-20 Aug. 70); XIV:10 (10-16 Mar. 72)
    - Berkeley Tribe 1970:19-26 June; 14-21 Aug.; 21-28 Aug. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Challenge, the Revolutionary Weekly (NY) (Box 29, Folder 3)
      I:11 (5 Sept. 1964); (report on US student visit to Cuba in I:11); Extra issue, n.d.
    - Columbia University Heights (Box 29, Folder 4)
      I:5 (25 Oct. 1967) (2 copies)
    - Connections "an underground newspaper, dedicated to remaining underground, rather than being buried above ground" (Madison, WI) (Box 29, Folder 5)
      I:1-4, 6,7; II:1-6, 9, 10, 12-14; III:1-9 (Mar. 1967-May 1969)
      - I:1 - nude w/gas mask on cover
      - II:3 - Special Issue: the Great Dow War
      - II:9 - incl. flyer aimed at faculty
      - III:1 - Chicago Convention Special
      - III:7 - black student demands
    - Cornell Chronicle (weekly) (Box 29, Folder 6)
      I:25,27, 29-31 (9 April-21 May 1970)
    - Cornell Daily Sun (Box 29, Folder 7)
      LXXXVI:49, 112-119, 122-125,127, 128, 130, 132, 136-140, 142 (17 Nov. 69-2 June 70)
      - no. 122 (20 Apr. 1970)
        -Daniel Berrigan appearing at Cornell.
      - no. 127 (27 Apr.)
        - article about court action against Robert Starobin and other students white and black, quoting him personally and incl. his joint statement about the university's frivolous and abusive use of court proceedings.
      - no. 139 (13 May)
        - with cover photo of Robert Starobin tossing flowers from a 'peace tank' after demonstration against ROTC on campus.
    - Crazy Times (La Jolla, CA) II:5 (7 Feb. 1972) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Daily Californian (Berkeley) 1, 2 Dec. 1966 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Daily Cardinal (Madison) -issues reporting on SDS and other campus radical news (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - 1966:5 Nov.
      - 1967: Jan. 31, Mar.3, Apr. 6, 25, 27, 28, 29, May 4, 5, 9-12, 17-20, Oct. 21, Nov. 17.
      - 1968: Mar. 28
      - 1970:Apr. 22-25, 28, 29, 30, May 1, 2, 5-9, 12-16, 18, 20, 22
      - 28 Apr. 1967- w/extra about students voting to have control over university affairs.
      - 28 Mar. 1968 - 1968 Registration Issue
      - 22 Apr. 1970 - special ecology issues printed in green
      - 29 Apr. 1970 - "Women Reborn"
      - 6 May 1970 - campus fires and violence
      - 22 May 1970 - mailed to Lyle Greenman in Madison who probably forwarded these issues to Robert Starobin.
    - the every other weekly (Berkeley) I:15 (10 Nov. 1970) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - F & M College Reporter (Franklin & Marshall College, Lancaster, PA) VI:32-34 (Feb. 1970), mimeo extra of VI:32 (Box 30, Folder 12)